<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OpenShift on Vincent Behar</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/tags/openshift/</link><description>Recent content in OpenShift on Vincent Behar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vincent.behar.name/tags/openshift/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Various OpenShift-related projects</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/creations/openshift-projects/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/creations/openshift-projects/</guid><description>In 2015-2016, while using OpenShift, I developed a few small open-source projects on top of the Kubernetes/OpenShift APIs:
OpenShift Dashboard OpenShift Cucumber OpenShift GitHub Hooks OpenShift/Git Integration OpenShift Flowdock Notifier OpenShift Dashboard When I started using OpenShift, I quickly realized that it was missing a global view of the cluster state. In August 2015 I developed a Web Dashboard for visualization of multi-projects resources in OpenShift.
This gave me the opportunity to learn the OpenShift/Kubernetes API early on, and improve my Go skills - by reading the OpenShift and Kubernetes code bases.</description></item><item><title>OpenShift</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/contributions/openshift/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/contributions/openshift/</guid><description>OpenShift is a Kubernetes &amp;ldquo;distribution&amp;rdquo; developed by Red Hat.
In the summer of 2015 I started using this newly announced platform, and as always when working with new projects, found a lot of opportunities for improvements.
This is how I contributed new features, bug fixes, bug reports and documentation in:
OpenShift Origin - including support for custom Dockerfile path when building Docker images OpenShift source-to-image - the tool used to build container images without using Dockerfiles OpenShift Documentation I also contributed to the OpenShift completion for oh-my-zsh plugin.</description></item></channel></rss>