<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>DevOps on Vincent Behar</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/tags/devops/</link><description>Recent content in DevOps on Vincent Behar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vincent.behar.name/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Interview with Digital Anarchist</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2019-12-interview-dwjw-lisbon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2019-12-interview-dwjw-lisbon/</guid><description>At the DevOps World | Jenkins World 2019 Conference in Lisbon, I was interviewed by Alan Shimel from Digital Anarchist.
We talked about:
Dailymotion Dailymotion&amp;rsquo;s ad-tech platform Technologies we use at Dailymotion: Cloud, Kubernetes, Jenkins X Practices we use at Dailymotion: Gitops Microservices and monoliths Why people go to conferences?</description></item><item><title>Confessions of an anonymous developer</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2011-04-article-cd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2011-04-article-cd/</guid><description>In 2011, I wrote a blog post on the Paris DevOps Meetup website, explaining on we adopted a DevOps mindset at RTL, step by step:
starting with basic communication tools, such as a common &amp;ldquo;chat&amp;rdquo; tool - Jabber - between devs and ops sharing data - logs - and tools to access them working together on automation tools getting devs to deploy their applications themselves and the impacts You can read the full blog post - in french.</description></item><item><title>Continuous Deployment with Jenkins and Rundeck</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2011-03-meetup-paris-devops/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2011-03-meetup-paris-devops/</guid><description>At the Paris DevOps meetup, at the march 2011 session, I gave a talk titled Continuous Deployment with Jenkins and Rundeck with my colleague Bruno.
Bruno presented Rundeck first, and how it can be used to automate operations.
And then I explained how we used it at RTL, to build a Continuous Deployment pipeline using Jenkins and Nexus:
for our staging environment, we enabled a continuous deployment workflow - which we called &amp;ldquo;0-click deployment&amp;rdquo; for our production environment, we enabled a continuous delivery workflow - which we called &amp;ldquo;1-click deployment&amp;rdquo; Read the full meetup report - in french.</description></item><item><title>Paris DevOps</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/creations/parisdevops/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/creations/parisdevops/</guid><description>In 2011, soon after the creation of the Paris DevOps Meetup group, I joined the team and help organize the meetups.
I built the parisdevops.fr using Jekyll on GitHub Pages: https://github.com/parisdevops/parisdevops.github.com
I wrote content on the website and organized meetups for a few months in 2011.</description></item></channel></rss>