<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Java on Vincent Behar</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/tags/java/</link><description>Recent content in Java on Vincent Behar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vincent.behar.name/tags/java/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Jenkins Rundeck Plugin</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/creations/jenkins-rundeck-plugin/</link><pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/creations/jenkins-rundeck-plugin/</guid><description>In 2011, I wrote a Jenkins plugin to integrate Rundeck as a &amp;ldquo;publisher&amp;rdquo;: the Rundeck plugin.
This plugin allows the creation of continuous delivery pipelines, using Jenkins to build your software and Rundeck to deploy it. I talked about it at the Paris DevOps meetup in march 2011: Continuous Deployment with Jenkins and Rundeck.
Note that this plugin is now maintained by the Rundeck team, and is still used by many people.</description></item><item><title>Rundeck API Java Client</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/creations/rundeck-api-java-client/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/creations/rundeck-api-java-client/</guid><description>In 2011, following the Jenkins Rundeck plugin, I extracted the code that talked to the Rundeck REST API into its own project: the Rundeck API Java Client.
The goal was to be able to write more software in Java using Rundeck&amp;rsquo;s REST API, for example the Rundeck Remote CLI, or writing scripts
Note that this project is now maintained by the Rundeck team at rundeck/rundeck-api-java-client, and is still used by many projects/people.</description></item><item><title>Cascading Flapi</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/creations/cascading-flapi/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/creations/cascading-flapi/</guid><description>In 2013, we were using Hadoop at Exalead, writing data processing pipelines with Cascading. But Cascading&amp;rsquo;s Java API was&amp;hellip; not very friendly to use.
I wanted a more &amp;ldquo;fluent&amp;rdquo; API, so I wrote an OSS project on top of Cascading to provide a fluent API. I used Flapi, which is an API generator for Java, &amp;ldquo;generating &amp;lsquo;smart&amp;rsquo; interfaces for improved fluency in your code&amp;rdquo;.
The cascading-flapi project was used at Exalead to help write our data processing pipelines&amp;hellip; until switching to Spark.</description></item><item><title>Rundeck</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/contributions/rundeck/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/projects/contributions/rundeck/</guid><description>Rundeck is an &amp;ldquo;open source automation service&amp;rdquo;. As explained in the Continuous Deployment with Jenkins and Rundeck talk I gave in 2011, Rundeck is an excellent tool to build a Continuous Deployment pipeline, on top of Jenkins.
I wrote a few contributions to Rundeck.</description></item></channel></rss>