<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Webinar on Vincent Behar</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/tags/webinar/</link><description>Recent content in Webinar on Vincent Behar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vincent.behar.name/tags/webinar/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>CI/CD on Kubernetes with Jenkins X</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2019-11-scaleup360/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2019-11-scaleup360/</guid><description>At the ScaleUp 360° Better Software digital event in november 2019, I gave a talk titled CI/CD on Kubernetes with Jenkins X.
In this talk, I explained how to do CI/CD on Kubernetes, and went through our experience using Jenkins X on GKE at Dailymotion:
What is Jenkins X Why and how we adopted Jenkins X at Dailymotion – and the benefits How we went from the &amp;ldquo;hello world&amp;rdquo; to the &amp;ldquo;real world&amp;rdquo;, and ended with the &amp;ldquo;2019 Most Innovative Jenkins X Implementation&amp;rdquo;: our custom implementation, and the integration of some open-source projects like Osiris (for auto-scaling to zero), sops (for secrets encryption) or Helmfile (to define our staging/production environments and handle deployments)</description></item><item><title>Our experience running Jenkins X in production</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2019-04-cdconference/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2019-04-cdconference/</guid><description>At the Continuous Delivery in a Cloud Native World virtual summit, in april 2019, I gave a talk titled Our experience running Jenkins X in production.
In this talk, I explained Dailymotion&amp;rsquo;s reasons for selecting Jenkins X to run the ad-tech platform CI/CD pipelines, and shared our experience using it in production:
how we keep our Preview Environments under control using Osiris to scale them down to 0 when they are not used how we promote our releases to staging/production on different Kubernetes clusters using Helmfile – and the benefits of it.</description></item></channel></rss>