<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Conference on Vincent Behar</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/tags/conference/</link><description>Recent content in Conference on Vincent Behar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://vincent.behar.name/tags/conference/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1 year with Jenkins X</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2019-12-dwjw-lisbon/</link><pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2019-12-dwjw-lisbon/</guid><description>At the DevOps World | Jenkins World 2019 Conference in Lisbon, I gave a talk titled 1 year with Jenkins X.
In this talk, I shared our experience using Jenkins X at Dailymotion for more than 1 year: how we went from the &amp;ldquo;hello world&amp;rdquo; to the &amp;ldquo;real world&amp;rdquo; with the &amp;ldquo;most innovative Jenkins X implementation&amp;rdquo;.
I explained how we adopted Jenkins X and its new practices – both on the organizational and technical side.</description></item><item><title>Interview with Digital Anarchist</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2019-12-interview-dwjw-lisbon/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2019-12-interview-dwjw-lisbon/</guid><description>At the DevOps World | Jenkins World 2019 Conference in Lisbon, I was interviewed by Alan Shimel from Digital Anarchist.
We talked about:
Dailymotion Dailymotion's ad-tech platform Technologies we use at Dailymotion: Cloud, Kubernetes, Jenkins X Practices we use at Dailymotion: Gitops Microservices and monoliths Why people go to conferences?</description></item><item><title>Our journey from Jenkins to Jenkins X</title><link>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2019-06-openrday/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://vincent.behar.name/publications/2019-06-openrday/</guid><description>At the Open R&amp;amp;Day 2019 Conference in Paris, I gave a talk titled Our journey from Jenkins to Jenkins X.
In this talk, I first introduced Jenkins X, and then went through some of the benefits we gained by switching Dailymotion ad-tech platform's CI/CD pipelines to Jenkins X: Preview Environments, easy promotion, Gitops, &amp;hellip;
I also explained how we adopted Jenkins X and did the migration, and finished with our open-source contributions as part of this migration.</description></item></channel></rss>