<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog Post on Vincent Behar</title><link>/tags/blog-post/</link><description>Recent content in Blog Post on Vincent Behar</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/blog-post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Zero cost preview environments on Kubernetes with Jenkins X and Osiris</title><link>/publications/2019-02-article-osiris/</link><pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/publications/2019-02-article-osiris/</guid><description>In february 2019, I wrote a blog post on Medium titled Zero cost preview environments on Kubernetes with Jenkins X and Osiris, explaining how to improve Jenkins X Preview Environments using Osiris, to automatically scale down to 0 the idle environments.
You can read the full blog post on Medium.</description></item><item><title>Dailymotion's journey from Jenkins to Jenkins X</title><link>/publications/2019-01-article-from-jenkins-to-jenkins-x/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/publications/2019-01-article-from-jenkins-to-jenkins-x/</guid><description>At the beginning of 2019, I wrote a blog post on Dailymotion's Medium publication titled Dailymotion's journey from Jenkins to Jenkins X.
It got more than 20k views in 1 year.
This story was also re-published on CloudBees blog.
You can read the full blog post on Medium.</description></item><item><title>Confessions of an anonymous developer</title><link>/publications/2011-04-article-cd/</link><pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/publications/2011-04-article-cd/</guid><description>In 2011, I wrote a blog post on the Paris DevOps Meetup website, explaining on we adopted a DevOps mindset at RTL, step by step:
starting with basic communication tools, such as a common &amp;ldquo;chat&amp;rdquo; tool - Jabber - between devs and ops sharing data - logs - and tools to access them working together on automation tools getting devs to deploy their applications themselves and the impacts You can read the full blog post - in french.</description></item></channel></rss>